=The Shoufu Can Read Mind=
= الشوفو يستطيع قراءة العقل =
=Episode 12=
= الحلقة 12 =
Who is so arrogant
المتعجرف جدا
to stop their vehicle in the palace?
لإيقاف سيارتهم في القصر؟
Miss,
يفتقد،
you shouldn't come here.
لا يجب أن تأتي إلى هنا.
If you're seen,
إذا رأيت ،
you'll be targeted.
سيتم استهدافك.
Am I that stupid?
هل أنا بهذا الغباء؟
I was thinking who is here in the middle of the street.
كنت أفكر بمن هو هنا في منتصف الشارع.
It's you, Miss Shen.
إنه أنت يا آنسة شين.
It's not weird anymore.
لم يعد الأمر غريباً بعد الآن.
Who is this?
من هذا؟
Miss,
يفتقد،
she's the daughter of Prince Ying,
إنها ابنة الأمير يينغ ،
Princess Ye Xiao'er.
الأميرة يي شياوئير.
I heard that
سمعت ان
Sir Xu has recently
السيد شو مؤخرا
married to a beautiful woman.
متزوج من امرأة جميلة.
If I remember it correctly,
إذا كنت أتذكرها بشكل صحيح ،
you've only been married for half a year.
أنت متزوج منذ نصف عام فقط.
You've disgusted your husband so quickly?
هل تشمئز زوجك بهذه السرعة؟
So pathetic.
مثير للشفقة.
You don't have to worry about it.
لا داعي للقلق بشأن ذلك.
You
أنت
are not young anymore.
لم يعودوا شبابًا.
You should quickly get married.
يجب أن تتزوج بسرعة.
You...
أنت...
Somebody!
شخص ما!
Punish her for me!
عاقبها من أجلي!
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
this is the name list
هذه قائمة الأسماء
of those who were cheating in the past imperial examinations,
من الذين كانوا يغشون في الامتحانات الإمبراطورية الماضية ،
and some Censors' accusation
وبعض اتهامات الرقباء
of Minister of Rites,
وزير الطقوس ،
Sir Zhou, for favouritism.
سيدي تشو ، من أجل المحسوبية.
Sir Xu, you've done your best for the imperial court.
سيدي شو ، لقد بذلت قصارى جهدك من أجل البلاط الإمبراطوري.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I dare not take any credits.
لا أجرؤ على أخذ أي اعتمادات.
It's
إنه
all General Shen
كل جنرال شين
and Shen Le's contribution in acting together with me.
ومساهمة شين لو في العمل معي.
Your Majesty, please understand.
جلالة الملك ، يرجى تفهم ذلك.
Everyone knows that
الجميع يعرف هذا
Shen Le is not smart.
شين لو ليست ذكية.
So, I
لذا أنا
helped him to get the high ranking.
ساعده في الحصول على مرتبة عالية.
Then,
ثم،
we can take the opportunity
يمكننا اغتنام الفرصة
to expose the cheating case.
لفضح قضية الغش.
Sir Xu,
سيدي شو ،
you're always thoughtful.
أنت دائمًا مدروس.
I know well about that.
انا اعرف جيدا عن ذلك
Here's my decree.
هذا هو مرسوم بلدي.
Arrest Minister of Rites, Zhou Kaiping,
اعتقال وزير الطقوس ، تشو كايبينغ ،
and his people
وشعبه
and jail them.
وسجنهم.
Report!
تقرير!
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
Princess Ye and...
الأميرة يي و ...
Madam Xu
سيدتي شو
are fighting outside the palace.
يقاتلون خارج القصر.
Is anyone injured?
هل جرح احد؟
I heard there is.
سمعت أن هناك.
- Get down here, - What are you doing?
- انزل هنا - ماذا تفعل؟
- Shen Zhihuan!
- شين تشيهوان!  - ماذا تفعل؟
- Get down here! - I'll beat you with my shoes!
- انزل هنا!  - سأضربك بحذائي!
Stay up there forever!
ابق هناك إلى الأبد!
Come up if you can!
تعال إذا استطعت!
You're clumsy.
أنت أخرق.
- I'm not listening! - Shen Zhihuan, get down here!
- أنا لست مصغيا!  - شين تشيهوان ، انزل هنا!
Shen Zhihuan, get down here!
شين تشيهوان ، انزل هنا!
Get down here!
انزل هنا!
Dan Zhu, let's go!
دان تشو ، دعنا نذهب!
Sir Xu,
سيدي شو ،
please help Miss Shen.
الرجاء المساعدة الآنسة شين.
We're in the imperial palace.
نحن في القصر الإمبراطوري.
What are you all doing?
ماذا تفعلون؟
Where's your manner?
أين طريقتك؟
Sir Xu, you're here in time.
سيدي شو ، أنت هنا في الوقت المناسب.
Your wife has injured me.
زوجتك جرحتني.
I can't let this slide.
لا أستطيع ترك هذه الشريحة.
Get down here.
انزل هنا.
(When I was climbing up here by stepping on them,)
(عندما كنت أتسلق هنا بالدوس عليها ،)
(I didn't know that the walls are so high.)
(لم أكن أعلم أن الجدران عالية جدًا).
Now, you're afraid.
أنت خائف الآن.
Why didn't you notice that it's dangerous?
لماذا لم تلاحظ أنه خطير؟
Stop mocking me.
توقف عن السخرية مني.
Dan Zhu,
دان تشو ،
get me a ladder.
أحضر لي سلم.
How long do you plan to stay up there?
كم من الوقت تخطط للبقاء هناك؟
Are you a monkey?
هل انت قرد
Jump down.
اقفز للاسفل.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.